[   
    {
        "question": "pies",
        "choice1": "cat",
        "choice2": "dog",
        "choice3": "pig",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "rower",
        "choice1": "car",
        "choice2": "house",
        "choice3": "bike",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "smok",
        "choice1": "dragon",
        "choice2": "phoenix",
        "choice3": "monster",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "kot",
        "choice1": "carpet",
        "choice2": "cat",
        "choice3": "fish",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "noga",
        "choice1": "leg",
        "choice2": "feet",
        "choice3": "head",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "kot",
        "choice1": "carpet",
        "choice2": "cat",
        "choice3": "fish",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "stół",
        "choice1": "table",
        "choice2": "mirror",
        "choice3": "chair",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "przyszłość",
        "choice1": "tomorrow",
        "choice2": "past",
        "choice3": "future",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "mózg",
        "choice1": "bone",
        "choice2": "brain",
        "choice3": "head",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "krzesło",
        "choice1": "table",
        "choice2": "chair",
        "choice3": "bottle",
        "answer": 2
    }
]